Read Jimmy's card to me please, Penny.
请把吉米的明信片念给我听听,Penny.
I have just arrived in Scotland and I'm staying at a Youth Hostel.'
“我刚到苏格兰,我现住在一家青年招待所.”
Eh?
He says he's just arrived in Scotland.
他说他刚到苏格兰.
He says he's staying at a Youth Hostel.
他说他现住在一家青年招待所.
You know he's a member of the Y.H.A.
您知道,他是“青招协”的一个成员.
The what?
什么?
The Y.H.A., Mum. The Youth Hostels Association.
“青招协”,妈妈.青年招待所协会.
What else does he say?
他还说了些什么?
I'll write a letter soon. I hope you are all well.'
“我很快会写信的.祝你们大家身体都好.”
What? Speak up. Penny.
什么?Penny,大声一点.
I'm afraid I can't hear you.
我恐怕我听不到你.
He say he'll write a letter soon.
他说他很快会写信的.
He hopes we are all well.
他祝我们大家身体好.
Love, Jimmy.'
“爱你的Jimmy.”
Is that all?
就这些吗?
He doesn't say very much,does he?
他没写许多,是吗?
He can't write very much on a card, Mum.
在明信片上他写不了很多,妈妈.